(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
んなあああああ！
Nnaaaaa!
みんな、おりゅ〜？
Everyone, are you here?
なのなのら！
Na no na no ra!
お菓子の国の お姫様
Princess of the candy kingdom,
とびきりプリティな ０歳児
An extraordinarily pretty 0-year-old.
ピアノだって 弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano,
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby, you know!
ワガママだって 言うけれど
They say I'm selfish, but...
ルーナはお姫様なのらから
...because Luna is a princess.
ルーナイト達も 執事も
The Lu-Knights and the butler too,
いちいちうるさいのら
Are annoying about every little thing.
さあルーナイト達！
Now, Lu-Knights!
準備はできたのら？
Are you ready?
出陣なのら〜！
It's time to deploy!
パフェもシュワシュワも
Parfaits and fizzy drinks too,
早く用意するのら！
Get them ready quickly!
あれもこれも食べたいのら
I want to eat this and that.
美味しいのは独り占め
I'll keep the delicious stuff to myself.
マズいのや苦いのは
The bad and bitter stuff...
ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
...are a gift for the Lu-Knights!
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains too,
キャンディの首飾りも
Candy necklaces too.
素敵なの たくさんあるのら
There are lots of wonderful things.
だからルーナのために
So for Luna's sake,
集めて来てね
Gather them all up, okay?
絶対 絶対 絶対 約束
Promise, promise, absolute promise.
なのなのら！
Na no na no ra!
まわる まわる まわる ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round.
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round even more.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って みんな
Spinning round and round, everyone.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って もっと
Laughing round and round even more.
ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って ずっと
Laughing round and round forever.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回るな (やあ！)
Spinning round and round, don't spin! (Yaa!)
ぐるぐる地球は 回り始め
The round earth began spinning...
幾億年
...billions of years ago.
いつまでもこのまま 回る
It will keep spinning like this forever...
みんなに幸せを
...bringing happiness to everyone.
回り続ける まわるルーナ
Keep on spinning, spinning Luna.
ますます 社会がぐるぐる ま〜
Society spins more and more... ro~
あれ？
Huh?
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Spinning round and round even more.
ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って みんな
Spinning round and round, everyone.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning round and round.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って もっと
Laughing round and round even more.
ぐるぐる 笑って
Laughing round and round.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って みんな
Dancing round and round, everyone.
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Dancing round and round.
まんなかちてん
Center Point
いつもはおとぎ話のお姫様
Usually, I'm a princess from a fairy tale.
みんなの輝くお月様
Everyone's shining moon.
今日はおやすみして
But I'm taking a break from that today.
重たい王冠今は置いといて
Setting aside this heavy crown for now.
どっちの私も好きになってくれますか
Will you fall in love with both versions of me?
どっちも欲しいから真ん中にいたくなるの
I want both, so I feel like staying right in the middle.
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt,
あるき出したんだ
I've started to walk.
出発のアラームは新しい
The departure alarm signals a new...
私が鳴らし始めるよ
...me starting to play the tune.
両腕をいっぱいにしても
Even if I fill my arms completely,
ぎゅっとしたいこの気持ち入らない
this feeling of wanting to hold you tight won't fit.
片方だけなんて選べない
I just can't choose only one side.
迷ってるなら真ん中なんだよ
If you're lost, then the answer is in the middle.
満開の青春
Youth in full bloom.
満腹に摂取
Intake to fullness.
満点流星群
Perfect score meteor shower.
満悦 In Heaven
Delight in Heaven.
満面な笑顔にして
With a big smile on your face.
満点すぎる思い出
Memories that are too perfect.
まんまるルーナ Happy Day!!
Round Luna Happy Day!!
世界の真ん中でプリンセスを
A princess in the center of the world,
忘れるくらい胸満タンに
filling my heart enough to forget everything else.
きゅんとしてみたい
I want to feel my heart skip a beat.
どっちだって本当の私
Either way, it's the real me.
瞬きしたら君のど真ん中
If I blink, I'm right in your center.
真ん中に重なる地点
The point overlapping in the middle.
真ん中で欲張る地点
The point of being greedy in the middle.
真ん中の真ん中地点
The middle of the middle point.
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best parts of a girl in love,
照れ隠しと素直の今 まんなかちてん
hiding embarrassment and being honest now. Center Point.
跪きなさい
Kneel down.
汝 この城の扉を叩いた者よ
You, who have knocked on the door of this castle.
誓いなさい
Pledge yourself.
このルーナの盾となり 矛となり
Become Luna's shield, become her spear.
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until I can sleep soundly at night,
共にあることを！
you shall be with me!
捧げなさい！
Dedicate yourself!
姫であるぞ！
I am the Princess!
守ってルナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight.
止まるな！
Don't stop!
なんて？
What?
紅茶のカップかちゃかちゃ鳴らさないでえらい
Not clinking the tea cup, good job.
スコーンだってこぼさず綺麗に食べてすごい
Eating scones cleanly without spilling, amazing.
たまな王冠どっちが前か間違っちゃうのかわいい
Sometimes mistaking which way the crown faces is cute.
通ってよし！なのら 開城！
You may pass! Nanora, open the gates!
ルナナイト第一条！
Luna Knight Article 1!
誰よりルーナが好きな人
Person who loves Luna more than anyone.
ルナナイト第二条！
Luna Knight Article 2!
シルクのお布団持って来て
Bring a silk futon.
ルナナイト第三条！
Luna Knight Article 3!
三時のお茶会来れる人
Person who can come to the 3 o'clock tea party.
守れなかったら即制裁！
If you can't keep them, immediate punishment!
分かって欲しいのら
I want you to understand, nanora.
これも帝王学を学ぶため
This is also to learn imperial studies.
愛という名の教育なのら
It's education in the name of love, nanora!
守ってルナナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me Luna Knight, if you don't think of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのなのら
I'll boycott the promenade, na no na no ra.
手の甲に忠誠 誓えるの？ ちゅっ
Can you pledge loyalty on the back of my hand? Chu.
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ
Put on the glass slipper and waltz.
守ってルナナイト 構ってくんないと
Protect me Luna Knight, if you don't pay attention to me,
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies and candies there are,
君がいなきゃだって みんな
if you aren't here... everyone.
心して
Be prepared...
捧げなさい！
and dedicate yourself!
姫であるぞ！
I am the Princess!
守ってルナナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me Luna Knight, if you don't think of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのなのら
I'll boycott the promenade, na no na no ra.
永遠の忠誠 この指に ちゅっ
Eternal loyalty to this finger. Chu.
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ
Put on the glass slipper and waltz.
守ってルナナイト 構ってくんないと
Protect me Luna Knight, if you don't pay attention to me,
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies and candies there are,
君がいなきゃだって みんな
if you aren't here... everyone.
心して
Be prepared...
捧げなさい！
and dedicate yourself!
姫であるぞ！
I am the Princess!
んなああああ！ みんなおりゅ？
Nnaaaaa! Is everyone here?
ホロライブ四期生 姫森ルーナなのら！
Hololive 4th Generation, Himemori Luna nanora!
今日はルーナたんの生誕祭ライブー！いえーい！
Today is Luna-tan's Birthday LIVE! Yay!
みんな来てくれてありがちゅ！
Thanks everyone for coming, arigachu!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
でれん！ #姫森ルーナ生誕LIVE2025
Deren! #HimemoriLunaBirthdayLive2025
これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
Please tweet a lot with this!
一曲目ね、どうだった？
How was the first song?
可愛かった？
Was it cute?
ふむふむ。ふむふむ。
Hmm hmm. Hmm hmm.
可愛い可愛い。
Cute, cute.
わかってたなのら。
I knew it nanora.
そして、今日のステージを見てください！
And then, please look at today's stage!
ダダダダダダダ！
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
すげー！雲だらけ！
Amazing! It's full of clouds!
あっちのさ...
Over there...
この雲の向こう、何があるなのらかな？
Beyond these clouds, I wonder what's there nanora?
みんな予想してみて！
Everyone, try to guess!
そして、今日のライブテーマは...
And then, today's live theme is...
Luna RebirthDay です！
Luna RebirthDay!
どんな意味があるのか。
What kind of meaning does it have?
はてさて。
Well, well.
そして、守ってルーナイト！
And, Protect Me Lu-Knight!
歌ってる時にね、
While singing,
ルーナたん、大変身しました！
Lunatan made a huge transformation!
みんな気づいてくれたなのら？
Did everyone notice nanora?
100万人記念で新モデルになりました！
For the 1 million commemoration, I became a new model!
イェーイ！
Yaaay!
そして、ポルナイトが...
And so, Poru-Knight...
ルーナたんに魔法をかけてくれたなのらよね。
cast magic on Lunatan nanora ne.
ポルナイト！
Poru-Knight!
おる〜？
Are you there~?
姫！姫！
Princess! Princess!
ほゆ？どこにいるなのら？
Hoyu? Where are you nanora?
姫〜！
Princess~!
わ！
Wa!
この雲の向こうにいます！
I'm beyond these clouds!
ほいよ〜！
Hoiyo~!
そうなのらね。
Is that so nanora ne.
ねぇねぇ、新しい姿...
Hey hey, the new appearance...
どう？どう？どう？
How is it? How is it?
え、めっちゃ可愛いよ！
Eh, it's super cute!
え、ほんとほんと？
Eh, really really?
せっかくだから、姫の以前の姿を出して
Since it's a special occasion, let's bring out Princess's previous appearance
比較してみよう！
and compare them!
あ、いいねいいねいいね！
Ah, nice nice nice!
おぉー！
Oooh!
どこどこどこ？あ、光ってる！出た！
Where where where? Ah, it's shining! It appeared!
出た、パネルが出そう！出た出た出た！
It appeared, the panel looks like it's coming out! It appeared!
え、見て！どう？変わった？変わった？
Eh, look! How is it? Changed? Changed?
ではまずは、足元から見ていきましょう！
Then first, let's look from the feet!
はい！
Yes!
あ、そうそうそう。あ、カメラさん。
Ah, yes yes yes. Ah, Camera-san.
いい感じですよ。
That's a good angle.
あれ？なんかこれ、影の感じとか変わった？
Huh? Like this, did the shadow feeling change?
変わった？変わった変わった？
Changed? Changed changed?
あああ！スカートとか、押し込められた感じ変わったね！
Aaa! The skirt and the tucked-in feeling changed!
可愛いじゃん！
It's cute!
ほよほよ、ほよほよ...
Hoyohoyo, hoyohoyo...
いい感じいい感じ？
Good feeling, good feeling?
待って。ここら辺。
Wait. Around here.
ここら辺とか待って。
Wait, around here and such.
これ、ガツトレーニングの効果出てるんじゃない！？
Hasn't the effect of gut training appeared here!?
え？出てる？出てるルーナたん？出てる？
Eh? Appearing? Is Lunatan appearing?
最近ガツトレーニングしてる？
Are you doing gut training lately?
やってるよ！パーソナルだけどな。
I'm doing it! Though it's personal training.
あ、そうそうだ。後ろ見て、後ろ後ろ！
Ah, right right. Look behind, behind!
え、後ろ？ほよ？
Eh, behind? Hoyo?
おおー！
Oooh!
これこれ！
This, this!
ね、見てこれ！髪の毛の揺れ！
Hey, look at this! The swaying of the hair!
あとシルエット感！
And the silhouette feeling!
これめっちゃいいじゃん！
This is super good isn't it!
すごー！
Amaaaazing!
えへへへ。
Ehehehe.
あと、あと！
Also, also!
そしてね、ルーナたんの手も見てほしいなのら！
And then, I want you to look at Lunatan's hand too nanora!
わぁ！
Waa!
お手手が、まぁー、小さくて可愛いね！
The hand is, wooooow, small and cute!
いいでしょ？手相もいい感じ。
Good right? The palm lines are also good feeling.
手相？あ、手相ね。
Palm lines? Ah, palm lines.
うん。
Yeah.
あと顔見て！
Also look at the face!
ああ！
Ah!
お顔、このパネルと比べるのはちょっと難しいんだけど、
Comparing the face with this panel is a little difficult but,
斜めから見た時の、あの...
When looked at from an angle, that...
フェイスラインとか変わったね！
Face line and such changed, didn't it!
変わった変わった！
Changed changed!
すごく可愛いじゃん！
It's super cute!
えへへへ。パパありがちゅー！
Ehehehe. Papa thank chu!
うん。ま、ぜひ...
Yeah. Well, by all means...
みんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べて欲しいなのら。
I want everyone to compare it with past 3D streams too nanora.
で、で、
Hey, hey,
ポル... ポルナイト？
Poru... Poru-Knight?
おう！
Oh!
質問があるなのらけど、
I have a question nanora but,
そっちの雲の向こうってどうなっているなのら？
What is happening beyond that cloud over there nanora?
舞踏会の会場あるよ！来る？
There's a ballroom venue! Coming?
え？マジ？
Eh? Seriously?
おいでよ！
Come here!
うん、バッシャーン！
Un, splash!
え、ば、バッシャーン？
Eh, sp-splash?
うわ、めっちゃ光ってる！
Uwa, it's shining super bright!
うわわわわわ！
Uwa wa wa wa wa!
デケー！
Huge!
これムーンギャラクシーの時、ステージにくっついてた馬車なのらよ！
This is the carriage that was attached to the stage during Moon Galaxy nanora yo!
というわけで姫！乗っちゃってください！
So, Princess! Please get on!
乗れるの？
Can I get on?
乗ってください！
Please get on!
乗るなのら〜！
I'm riding nanora~!
うわぁー！すごい！中も豪華なのら〜！
Uwaaa! Amazing! The inside is gorgeous too nanora~!
ちょっとここ座ってみるなのら。よいしょ。
I'll try sitting here a bit nanora. Yoisho.
ルーナイトの人形も居るなのらね。
There's a Lu-Knight doll too nanora ne.
すごー！
Amaaaazing!
姫！準備はOKですか？
Princess! Is the preparation OK?
OKなのら！出発進行なのら〜！
OK nanora! Depart progress nanora~!
よし！飛びますよ〜！
Alright! We're flying~!
行くぞ〜！
Let's go~!
わ！動いた！
Wa! It moved!
うぉー、進むぞー！
Uooo, it's advancing!
すげー！この馬車飛んでるなのら〜！
Amazing! This carriage is flying nanora~!
よし。よいしょ。こっち見てみよう。
Alright. Yoisho. Let's look this way.
うわぁー！すごー！星と雲がめっちゃ綺麗なのら〜！
Uwaaa! Amaaaazing! The stars and clouds are super pretty nanora~!
うわ、眺め最高なのらね。
Uwa, the view is the best nanora ne.
ガタンゴトン、揺れてますわ〜。
Rumble rumble, it's shaking wa~.
いいなのら。こっちからも見てみるなのらね。
It's good nanora. I'll try looking from here too nanora ne.
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Yoisho, yoisho.
こっちもすごい！眺め最高！
This side is also amazing! The view is the best!
うわ、いい感じなのら。
Uwa, good feeling nanora.
高いなのらね、ここ。
It's high nanora ne, here.
でもポルナイトさ... このまま進んだら目の前のデッカイ雲とぶつかるなのらけどさ...
But Poru-Knight... if we keep going like this, we'll crash into the big cloud in front nanora but...
大丈夫なのら...？
Is it okay nanora...?
見えねえのよ
I can't see it!
いや、ご安心ください。このポルナイトにお任せあれ。
No, please rest assured. Leave it to this Pol-Knight.
姫、少々揺れますぞ！しっかり掴まっててください！
Princess, it will shake a little! Please hold on tight!
え？大丈夫これ本当に？
Eh? Is this really okay?
飛ぶぞ！
We're taking off!
本当に大丈夫！？
Are you really sure!?
野蛮ちゃん出るかな…雲来てるよ！
Will savages show up...? The clouds are coming!
わ、もう来る！？
Wha- It's coming already!?
うわああああああ！
Waaaaah!
あたし今 最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest I've ever been right now.
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm the cutest I've ever been.
これが乙女の逆襲だ
This is a maiden's counterattack.
もう気づいてるかも
You might have already noticed,
しれないけど言うわ
but I'm going to say it anyway.
あたしね 今とてもかわいい
You know, I'm really cute right now.
君が始めた恋
The love that you started,
君が終わらすなんて
for you to be the one to end it,
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
what's with that? I'm gonna cry.
かわいい
Cute!
あたしの連絡だけ
Only messages from me,
通知オフにしてたなんて
you had notifications turned off for them.
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend.
連絡しすぎだって
That I messaged too much,
君を不安にさせるからじゃん
it's because you made me anxious!
もう気にしてないけど
I don't care anymore though.
だって今
Because right now,
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm the cutest I've ever been.
自分史上いちばん ときめき放つわ
I'm releasing the most sparkle in my history.
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest I've ever been.
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ
Admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack.
流石に失恋直後は
Naturally, right after the heartbreak,
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで
I was a mess with tears.
かわいい
Cute!
君が泣かせたのに
Even though you made me cry,
雑なサヨナラだった
it was such a sloppy goodbye.
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What's with that? I'm gonna cry.
かわいい
Cute!
二人しか知らないって
That only the two of us knew,
言ってた話だって
the stories you said,
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
why does that girl know them too?
別れてよかったなんて
That it was good we broke up,
思わせないで欲しかった
I didn't want you to make me think that.
好きだったから
Because I loved you.
君に振られて最上級に可愛くなりました
After being dumped by you, I became the cutest I've ever been.
むしろありがと 最上級に可愛くなったって
Actually, thank you. That I became the cutest ever,
ねえ言って？
hey, say it?
あいつがなんか可愛くなったって
That she somehow became cuter,
ねえ聞いて
hey, listen.
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm the cutest I've ever been.
自分史上いちばん ときめき放つわ
I'm releasing the most sparkle in my history.
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest I've ever been.
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ
Admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack.
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest I've ever been.
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm the cutest I've ever been.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日
A boring Monday.
あなたの香りで目覚めるの
I wake up to your scent.
纏ったトップノート
The top note I wore,
そうよ秘密の物語なの
yes, it's a secret story.
うまくリプライできない
I can't reply well.
震えるハート
My trembling heart.
ためらい 恥じらい 空回り
Hesitation, shyness, spinning wheels.
誘うファンタジー
Inviting fantasy,
重なっちゃうくらい
enough to overlap,
一途だもん
because I'm devoted.
あなたに夢中です
I'm crazy about you.
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃヤダ
Ah, going viral, going viral, no way!
ねえ 構って構って もっと
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more.
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is aiming for you.
ウィンクひとつで メロメロにさせちゃって
Making them fall head over heels with just a wink,
こっちの気も知らないで
without even knowing how I feel.
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃヤダ
Geez! Going viral, going viral, no way!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いて ずっと
Hey, shoot through, shoot through my heart forever.
いつでもあなたに翻弄中
I'm always at your mercy.
誰よりあなたの特別でいさせて
Let me be your special one more than anyone else.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what path awaits,
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run through with glass heels!
魔法が解けても
Even if the magic spell breaks,
醒めない夢を
a dream I won't wake from,
あなたにあげる
I'll give to you.
だからぜったい！
So absolutely!
負けない！
I won't lose!
約束した
I promised!
純愛
Pure love!
したい！
I want to do it!
まっすぐに
Straight ahead!
想うパッション
My feelings of passion,
伝わっちゃうくらい
enough to get through to you,
本気だもん
because I'm serious!
まさしく
Truly,
無敵です！
I am invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ
Ah, fall for me, it's okay to fall for me!
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと
Hey, realize it, realize it properly!
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A maiden in love is ever-changing.
綺麗もキューティーも
Both beauty and cuteness,
欲張りに励めば
if I strive greedily for both,
輝く自分になるの
I'll become a shining version of myself.
さあ！ ハマってハマっていいよ
Come on! Fall for me, it's okay to fall for me!
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと
Hey, realize it, realize it properly!
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A maiden is still making rapid progress.
世界で一番の
The number one in the world,
ドキドキがほしいの
I want the heart-pounding excitement.
あなたしかいない
There is only you,
プリンスですっ
my prince!
Ah 「好き」って
Ah, 'like'...
「好き」ってなんで
why do I say 'like'?
そう ズキって
Yes, it throbs...
ズキって言うの？
why does it throb?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My admirable heart is in confusion.
愛しさふくらんで
My affection swells,
こんなにも苦しいの
it's so painful like this.
いますぐこっちに笑って！
Smile at me right now!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ！
Ah, going viral, going viral, no way!
ねえ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is aiming for you.
ウインクひとつで
With just one wink,
メロメロにさせちゃって
making you fall madly in love,
こっちの気もしらないで！
without even knowing my feelings!
もー！ バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ！
Geez! Going viral, going viral, no way!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, shoot through, shoot through my heart forever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄中
I'm always being toyed with by you.
誰よりあなたの
More than anyone else,
トクベツでいたいの
I want to be your special one.
罠で出たかな？
Did I set a trap?
許してね
Forgive me, okay?
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Love love you, fluffy fluffy foo!
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a melo-melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
オトナじゃない
I'm not an adult,
オトメです。
I'm a maiden.
恋するのが仕事です
Falling in love is my job.
君の名前
When I whisper,
つぶやくと
your name,
ドキドキするの
my heart pounds.
聞き分けいない
Disobedient,
この胸が
this heart of mine,
歌い出して止まらない
starts singing and won't stop.
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry for not being good at it,
だけど聞いて
but please listen.
とどけ
Reach you,
マイメロディー
My Melody!
星空を越えて
Crossing the starry sky,
君の夢 守るリボン
the ribbon that protects your dreams.
マイメロディー
My Melody!
ハート見つけたなら
If you find a heart,
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up round and round, okay?
Wo wo wo
覚悟しといて
be prepared!
ウソじゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない
I'm not an adult,
オトメです。
I'm a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even cry sometimes.
女の子って
Girls are,
魔法で
made of,
作られたの
magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Love love you, fluffy fluffy foo!
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a melo-melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
キライじゃない
I don't hate you,
ってゆーかスキ
or rather, I love you!
スナオになんてなれません
I can't be honest with myself.
君の笑顔
Just seeing,
見るだけで
your smile,
フニャフニャするの
makes me go all soft.
それなのに
And yet,
and yet,
憎まれ口 撃ちまくり
I keep firing off hateful words.
ひとりになって落ち込んで
I get depressed when I'm alone,
枕パンチ！！
and punch my pillow!!
だから
So,
マイメロディー
My Melody!
本当の気持ち
My true feelings,
風になって結ぶリボン
become the wind and tie the ribbon.
マイメロディー
My Melody!
歌えオトメゴコロ
Sing, maiden's heart!
マイメロディー 歌えオトメゴコロ
My Melody, sing maiden's heart.
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえ
Love is coming, catch it!
wow wow wo 逃がさないから
wow wow wo, I won't let you get away.
ここへ来て
Come here.
キライじゃない ツライです(T_T)
I don't hate it, it's painful (T_T).
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I'm even turning bright red.
女の子って不思議で作られたの
Girls are made of mysteries.
届け マイメロディー
Reach them, My Melody.
マイメロディー
My Melody.
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
Crossing the starry sky, the ribbon that protects your dream.
マイメロディー
My Melody.
ハート見つけたなら
If you find a heart,
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up round and round!
wow wow wo 覚悟しといて
wow wow wo, be prepared!
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです
Not an adult, a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even cry sometimes.
女の子って魔法で作られたの
Girls are made of magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki suki su, fuwa fuwa fu~
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling, melo-melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディー
Please, My Melody.
わぁー！ということで！
Waaa! So...
「最上級にかわいいの！」と
With 'Saijoukyu ni Kawaii no!'...
「ひたむきシンデレラ」
...'Hitamuki Cinderella'...
あと「オトメロディー」
...and 'Otome-lody'!
3曲連続で歌いました！
I sang three songs in a row!
んなぁ〜
Nnaaaa~
雲が晴れたステージってこうなってるのらね！
So this is what the stage looks like with the clouds cleared!
すげぇ でっけぇ！
It's super huge!
舞踏会みたいなんのらね！
It looks just like a ballroom!
あ、ここ見て！シャンデリアがあるのら！
Ah, look here! There's a chandelier!
ザ・舞踏会 ダンスするって場所なのらね！
The Ballroom! It's a place for dancing!
あと、お城の上の方ってこうなってたんだ！
Also, the top of the castle looked like this!
見て！すごい可愛い！
Look! It's super cute!
ほらほら これ天窓じゃん！
Look, look! It's a skylight!
わぁーお 綺麗なのらね！
Wow! It's beautiful!
すごい！あ、待って！
Amazing! Ah, wait!
Luna RebirthDayの看板もあるのら！
There's even a sign for Luna RebirthDay!
今日はLuna RebirthDayだからな
Because today is Luna RebirthDay.
見て見て！すごい可愛い！
Look, look! It's super cute!
なんだ なんだ なんだ？
What? What? What is it?
最高だったよ！
It was the best!
え？ なにこれ？
Eh? What is this?
フルナイトやらないかい？
Aren't you a Full Knight?
実はね 姫には...
Actually, Princess...
まだ隠された姿が残されているのです！
...still has a hidden form remaining!
え？ なん なん なん なのら？
Eh? W-W-What is it?
フルナイトの魔法で
With Full Knight's magic...
そのお姿にしてみせましょう！
...I will reveal that form!
え、なに？ はぁー！あつ！
Eh, what? Haa! Hot!
溶けた 溶けた 溶けた！
It's melting, melting, melting!
ててーん！
Ta-da!
うわぁー！すごい！
Waaa! Amazing!
可愛い！新しいヘアスタイルなのらな！
Cute! It's a new hairstyle!
フルナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのらね？
Full Knight presented this to me, right?
うぅっ...
Ugh...
よし じゃあこの新しい髪型で
Alright, then with this new hairstyle...
歌っちゃうのら！
...I'm gonna sing!
あなたのアイドル
Your Idol...
サインはB！
...Sign is B!
(Chu-！)
(Chu-!)
L-O-V-E ラブリー ルーナたん！
L-O-V-E Lovely Luna-tan!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
Finally met you, so happy.
待ち遠しくて 足をバタバタしながら
Couldn't wait, stamping my feet.
今日楽しみで 寝れなかったよ
Looked forward to today, couldn't sleep!
(オレモー！)
(Me too!)
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
No time to be nervous.
1分1秒 無駄になんてできない
Can't waste a minute or a second.
さぁ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin!
君も！
You too!
君も！ お待ちどうさま
You too! Thanks for waiting!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome!
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where 'love' gathers.
日常はクロークの中
Leave daily life in the cloakroom.
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ
Since you're here, gotta dance!
損！損！損！
Loss! Loss! Loss!
人が居ようが居まいが関係ない
Doesn't matter if people are watching.
(関係ない！)
(Doesn't matter!)
箱が大きい小さいとか気にしない
Don't care if the venue is big or small.
(気にしない！)
(Don't care!)
ちゃんと見えてる
I can see clearly,
君のサイリウム！
Your cyalume!
今はフーっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it might blow away with a puff,
小さな小さな才能だけど
Such a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
...if you support me...
If you are going to support me as your 'Oshi',
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you the ultimate fan service!
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol,
サインはB
the sign is B!
Chu！
Chu!
あいつ俺が育てたって
Saying 'I'm the one who raised her',
近い将来 自慢してほしいよ
I want you to boast about that in the near future.
こうしちゃいられない
We can't just stand around!
君と！
With you!
今を！
Right now!
楽しまなきゃ損
It's a loss if we don't enjoy it!
引きこもりも人見知りも
Shut-ins and shy people alike,
普段と違う顔見せてよ
show me a face you don't usually show!
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
We're all siblings, how are you doing?
なりふり構わずに
Without caring about appearances,
そう！
Yeah!
他人に笑われていても
Even if others laugh at us,
関係ない
it doesn't matter!
周りがどうとかこうとか
I don't care about what people around us say,
気にしない
I won't pay it any mind!
主張
Assertiveness
強すぎ
is too strong,
君のサイリウム！
your cyalume (glow stick)!
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me,
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
and even if I feel all alone,
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
as long as you are on my side,
怖いものはないよ
there is nothing to fear!
B小町！ フッフー！
B-Komachi! Fu-fuu!
見てよ 見てよ
Look here, look here!
何か始まる
Something is starting,
君との物語が
our story together.
嗚呼
Ah,
なんて素晴らしい景色だ！
what a magnificent view!
客席が居ようが
Whether there is an audience
居まいが関係ない
or not, it doesn't matter.
会場が大きい
Whether the venue is big
小さいとか気にしない
or small, I don't care.
ちゃんと見えてる
I can see it clearly,
君のサイリウム！
your cyalume!
今はフーっと吹けば
Right now, if you blow on it,
飛ぶような
it might just fly away,
小さな小さな才能だけど
it's a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you are going to support me,
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
and if you stay on my side,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you the ultimate fan service!
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol,
サインはB
the sign is B!
Chu！
Chu!
最高！最高！
The best! The best!
絶対結婚しようね！
Let's absolutely get married!
ロマンスの不祥事
A romantic scandal,
逃がさない
I won't let it escape.
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you,
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
Sil Vu President.
宣誓！
I pledge!
私が大統領になったら
If I become the President,
人の男にちょっかいかける女は
women who mess with other people's men
島流しにします
will be exiled to an island!
宣誓！
I pledge!
私が大統領になったら
If I become the President,
いやただの友達だよ～って
guys who lie saying 'we're just friends'
誤魔化す奴は
to smooth things over,
ヘソから電気を流します
will be electrocuted through their belly buttons!
大胆不敵
Fearless and daring,
センセーショナルクローズアップ
sensational close-up.
D, D, D, Don't cry
やるぜ徹底的に
I'll do it thoroughly,
リサーチだ
it's an investigation!
大嫌い？
You hate me?
しょうがない？
Can't be helped?
クズは病気ね
Being scum is a disease,
バイバイバイ
bye bye bye!
権力！
Power!
財産！
Fortune!
地位名声！
Status and fame!
なんにもないけど
I have none of those,
裁きたい！
but I want to judge you!
でしょ？
Right?
ワン ツー スリー
One, two, three.
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the P-P-P-President,
まずは君を捕まえるね
first, I'll capture you.
濡れたタオルで
Using a wet towel,
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you confess everything.
誰ですか あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか そうですか
Is it no good? Is that so?
(あちゃ〜)
(Oh no~)
ロマンスの不祥事
A romantic scandal,
逃がさない
I won't let it escape.
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you,
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
Sil Vu Pre-Pre-President.
宣誓！
I pledge!
私が大統領になったら
If I become the President,
ただの仕事の付き合いだよ？
'It's just a work relationship'
っていう奴は
- anyone who says that
二度と働けなくしてやります
will never be able to work again!
宣誓！
I pledge!
以下略！
Et cetera!
いや向こうが強引でさ〜
Guys who say 'She was just so pushy'
っていう男の口には
- into their mouths,
レジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
I'll pour resin and harden it shut!
密着 まるでドン・ファン気取り
Too close, acting like a Don Juan,
スキャンダラス
it's scandalous.
末端価格
Street value?
甲斐性なしの
For a worthless person,
スクープね
it's quite a scoop.
愛はない？
There's no love?
理由じゃない
That's no excuse.
悪くないのに
You're not bad, but...
はいはいはい
yeah, yeah, yeah.
軽薄！
Frivolous!
能脳！
No-brain!
イケシャアシャア！
Shameless!
なんにもないとか
Saying 'nothing happened',
ありえないでしょ？
that's impossible, right?
ワン ツー スリー
One, two, three.
だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね
Even if I become the P-P-P-President,
多分君は変わらないね
you probably won't change.
しらっととぼけて
Playing innocent smoothly,
のらりくらりかわすのね
you dodge the questions lazily.
デートですか
Is this a date?
こんばんは
Good evening.
本気ですか
Are you serious?
そうですか
Is that so?
(ぽちっ)
(Click)
情熱とは不注意
Passion is carelessness,
微熱も
even a slight fever,
消してしまいたい
I want to erase it all.
One, two, three
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the P-P-P-President,
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll seriously arrest you, okay?
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel,
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you confess every single thing.
どこですか 今あんた
Where are you right now, dear?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
Found you! Busted!
夜道にはご用心 さよなら
Be careful on the night roads, goodbye.
かわりに銃声
Instead, a gunshot.
シル・ヴ・プレプレ・プレジデント
S'il vous pla-pla-President!
て・て・て・トップ・テレスター 勘弁週は
Te-te-te-top telestar, pardon week...
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
あなたにもう忘れたいこと
Things I want you to forget already,
悲しいこと あるのかしらね
I wonder if there are sad things for you.
知らない映画なのに
Even though it's a movie I don't know,
涙を流すのは
The reason I shed tears is...
どの街角が足りてないからよ
...because some street corner is missing.
繋ぐにもつかないこと
Things that can't even be connected,
くだらないこと
Trivial things,
考えてばかりね
That's all you think about.
雨が上がれば愛も
If the rain stops, love too...
その行く顔も
...and that passing face,
誰かのものになるでしょう
Will become someone else's, right?
そっぱちのファンデーションも全部
All that cheap foundation,
恋のためよ
It's all for love.
なになに いったいぜんたい
What, what? In the world...
どうして どうして なぜ なぜ 果てな
Why, why, why, why? No end.
不安定なカンテナ
Unstable antenna,
どこまで行くの
How far will it go?
あなた一切合切
You, everything and anything,
放り去っても
Even if you throw it all away...
冗談じゃないないわ
It's not a joke, no way.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって
Even if that time comes,
どうにもなんないぜ
It won't help anything.
曖昧な
Vague...
本当なんて目眩がするだけ
...truths only make me dizzy.
あたしを浚って今
Sweep me away, right now,
チック・タック・イエス
Tick-tock, yes.
ああ 全然おかしなハートばかり
Ah, nothing but totally weird hearts,
食指がピクリともしないわ
My appetite isn't piqued at all.
実体のない感情
Formless emotions,
放っておいたって
Even if left alone,
策略なんてありゃせんのに なぜ
There's no scheme involved, so why?
ああ もう懲り懲りよ
Ah, I'm already sick of it.
あたしの空回るキスも
My kisses spinning in vain,
じっと堪えて
Enduring patiently,
取り繕っては
Keeping up appearances,
とうとう臨界点
Finally at the critical point.
年がら年中
All year round,
リップサービス
Lip service.
鈍感かましては
Playing dense,
僻易
I'm fed up.
行き当たりばったり
Haphazardly,
ドンガラガッシャン
Crash and burn!
昼下がりは涙の目に鬼
In the early afternoon, a demon in teary eyes.
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいで
Now, because of the music in my head,
あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
I can't hear a word you're saying.
少しはまともなこと言って
Say something sensible for once,
いえ
No.
周り出した
It started spinning,
ターンテーブルで全部
Everything on the turntable,
忘れさせてよ
Make me forget it all.
だけど一体全体
But what in the world,
どうして どうして なぜ なぜ 果てな
Why, why, why, why? No end.
冗談じゃないないわ
It's not a joke, no way.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって
Even if that time comes,
どうにもなんないぜ
It won't help anything.
曖昧な
Vague...
本当なんて目眩がするだけ
...truths only make me dizzy.
あたし 今
I am... right now...
冗談じゃないないわ
It's not a joke, no way.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって
Even if that time comes,
どうにもなんないぜ
It won't help anything.
不甲斐ないわ
It's pathetic.
感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
I'll just wash emotions away at the laundry.
あたしと
With me...
確かめ合っている マジ？
...confirming each other. Seriously?
アイ ヤイヤイヤー
Ai-ya-ya-ya.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって
Even if that time comes,
どうにもなんないぜ
It won't help anything.
曖昧な
Vague...
本当なんて目眩がするだけ
...truths only make me dizzy.
あたしを浚って今
Sweep me away, right now,
チック・タック・イエス
Tick-tock, yes.
二酸化炭素を吐き出して
Breathing out carbon dioxide,
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
That child is breathing.
曇天模様の空の下
Under the cloudy sky,
つぼみのままで揺れながら
Swaying while still a bud.
野良犬は僕の骨くわえ
The stray dog holds my bone in its mouth,
野生の力を試してる
Testing its wild power.
路地裏に月が落っこちて
The moon fell into the back alley,
犬の目玉は四角だよ
And the dog's eyeballs are square.
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time, humanity...
木星に着いたよ
...arrived at Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
...has gotten closer.
花火の笛の音響く
The sound of fireworks whistling echoes.
街の外れの夢の跡
At the remains of dreams on the outskirts of town.
翼を失くしたペガサスが
A Pegasus that has lost its wings,
夜空に梯子をかけている
Is placing a ladder against the night sky.
武器をかついだ兵隊さん
A soldier carrying a weapon,
南に行こうとしてるけど
Is trying to go south, but...
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと
The clinking sound of sabers,
街の空気を汚してる
Is polluting the air of the town.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humankind...
木星についたよ
Has arrived at Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
Is getting closer.
歌を忘れたカナリヤ
A canary that has forgotten its song.
牛を忘れた牛小屋
A cowshed that has forgotten the cows.
こわれた磁石を拾いあつめる
Gathering up broken magnets,
博士はまるはげさ
The professor is completely bald.
あの子は花火を打ち上げて
That girl launches fireworks,
この日が来たのを祝ってる
Celebrating that this day has come.
冬の花火は強すぎて
The winter fireworks are too strong,
僕らの身体は砕け散る
And our bodies are shattering.
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree,
僕はあの子を探すけど
I search for that girl, but...
月の光に邪魔されて
Hindered by the moonlight,
あの子のかけらは見つからない
I can't find any fragments of her.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humankind...
木星についたよ
Has arrived at Jupiter.
ついたー！
We arrived!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
Is getting closer.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humankind...
木星についたよ
Has arrived at Jupiter.
ついたー！
We arrived!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
Is getting closer.
サルにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey.
こわれた磁石を砂浜で
Picking up broken magnets on the sandy beach...
拾っているだけさ
Is all I'm doing.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humankind...
木星についたよ
Has arrived at Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
Is getting closer.
サルになるよ
We'll become monkeys.
あぁ...
Ah...
朝まで踊る
Dancing until morning,
夢だけ見せて
Show me only dreams.
時計の鐘が解く魔法
The clock's bell breaks the magic.
曖昧な指
Vague fingers,
誘う階段
The alluring staircase.
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
Leaping up three steps at a time.
馬車の中で
Inside the carriage,
震えてた
I was trembling.
みじめな古着
Miserable old clothes,
めくりめぐれ夜の舞踏
Turn over, go round, the night's ball.
深くあの声が
That voice deep down...
握り締めた刃
The blade I held tight...
突き立て
Thrust it in...
すべてを奪えと
And steal everything.
孤児集う城
The castle where orphans gather.
笑み仮面に描いて
Drawing a smile on the mask,
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false affection...
羽で包む熾天使
Is wrapped in wings by the Seraph.
灰の中で
In the ashes,
赤く溶けて混じる
Melting red and mixing together.
硝子の靴
Glass slippers.
今更帰る
Going home now?
震えているの
Are you trembling?
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you glance at...
靴脱ぎ踊る
Kick off the shoes and dance,
スロープ抜けて
Through the slope.
喉まで伸びる指の先で
With fingertips reaching up to the throat,
すくう雫
Scooping the drop,
口付けて
Kiss it.
走る衝動
Running impulse,
背骨抜けていく
Running through the spine.
刹那
In that moment.
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't ring the bell.
あなたにひざまずき
Kneeling to you,
まだダメと叫んだ右手が
My right hand screamed "not yet"...
突き刺すサヨナラ
Thrusting a goodbye.
消せない硝煙を
The unerasable gunpowder smoke,
香水にまとう姫
A princess clad in perfume.
強い瞳
With strong eyes,
僕の凍った仮面ごと撃ち抜く
Shoot through my frozen mask.
今も耳に
Even now in my ears,
あなたの吐息が
Your sigh...
突き刺さるの
Pierces me.
遠い夢
A distant dream.
ステンドグラス越し
Through the stained glass,
光る月が
The glowing moon...
君にかぶせたベール
Is the veil draped over you.
ドレス膝で裂いて
Tearing the dress with knees,
ティアラは投げ捨てて
Throwing away the tiara.
見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Eyes meeting eyes,
火花を放つ
Sparks fly.
孤独な魂が
Lonely souls...
炎あげ惹かれあう
Raise flames and attract each other.
その涙すくえないなら
If I can't save those tears,
まるで一人遊び
It's like playing alone.
時よ止まれ今は
Time, stop, for now...
あなたに酔いしれて
Intoxicated by you.
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを
Every single wavering heartbeat...
刻み付けたい
I want to carve it in.
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay, get hot and wet,
打ち付ける高まりに
To the pounding excitement.
これ以上は動けないよ
I can't move anymore than this.
まるで御伽噺
Just like a fairy tale.
みんな！ここからは大事な告知タイムなのら！
Everyone! From here on, it's important announcement time!
パパ！パパはそこで見ててなのらね！
Papa! Papa, you watch from over there, okay!
ではまずはこちら！
Now then, first is this!
テデン！
Ta-da!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025のグッズだ... す！
It's the Himemori Luna Birthday Commemoration 2025 goods!
ではこちら詳細見ていきましょう！
Now let's look at the details!
テデン！
Ta-da!
ふたりのルーナ アクリルジオラマスタンドなのら！
It's the "Two Lunas" Acrylic Diorama Stand!
イラストはソイルン先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Soyln-sensei!
前のね、髪型と、今回のルーナのね、新しい髪型のルーナが...
The previous hairstyle, and this time's Luna's, the new hairstyle Luna...
そして今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました！
And they appeared on the stage of this birthday live!
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが華やかな...
This one has gorgeous three-dimensional parts...
可愛い、素敵な、豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになっております！
It's a cute, wonderful, and luxurious diorama stand!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
テデン！
Ta-da!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ、守ってルーナイトver.ちゃん！
Himemori Luna Plushie, Protect Me Lu-Knight Version!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ 守ってルーナイトver.
Himemori Luna Plushie: Protect Me Luna Knight ver.
みんなさんがぬいぐるみになりましたー！いえいえいえい！
Everyone, you've become a plushie! Yay yay yay!
ぜひぜひ みんなお家にお迎えして
Please welcome one to your home,
あなたをね 守ってほしいのらよ
and have it protect you, nora!
そして 次はこちら
And next is this!
ででん！ルーナイト2wayバッグ♡
Ta-da! Luna Knight 2-Way Bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまう
The plushie from before fits right inside,
ルーナイトがアピールできるバッグとなってます
making it a bag where you can show off your Luna Knight pride.
バッグはね なんとリュックにもなって超便利！
The bag actually turns into a backpack too, super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは
The motifs used in the design
ルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので
are all based on Luna Knights,
バッグモードでも リュックモードでも
so whether in bag mode or backpack mode,
お好きな方で使ってください
please use it however you like.
次は こちら
Next is this.
ででん！ルーナイトカードホルダー♡
Ta-da! Luna Knight Card Holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです
It's a card holder shaped like a Luna Knight.
チェキ風カードや ホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので
You can fit Cheki-style cards or Holo Cards inside,
ルーナイトのみんなは こっちもしっかり守ってくださいね
so all you Luna Knights, make sure to protect this too, okay?
そして 次はこちら
And next is this.
ででん！ASMRボイス
Ta-da! ASMR Voice.
「舞踏会の帰り道」
"On the Way Home from the Ball."
今回はね 舞踏会をイメージした生誕祭ライブなので
Since this birthday live is themed around a ball,
ルーナイトと帰路についた ひとときをボイスにしました
I made a voice pack about the moment we head home together.
馬車の中という密室で
In the closed space of a carriage...
なんか急接近とかあったちゃうかもー？
we might suddenly get super close?
ということで 最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょう
So, let's take a look at the full set one last time.
こちら フルセット購入特典は
The Full Set Purchase Bonus is...
ででん！オリジナルカード！
Ta-da! Original Card!
イラストはジョー・イリノ先生で
The illustration is by Joe Irino-sensei,
表面がチェキ風のカードになってます
and the front is a Cheki-style card.
裏面は 招待状風のデザインになっていてオシャレなのら
The back has a stylish invitation-style design, nora.
そして 通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
And the Regular Version Full Set Bonus is...
箔押し複製サイン入り チェキ風ブロマイドカード
a foil-stamped duplicate signed Cheki-style bromide card.
そして 数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
And the Limited Quantity Version Full Set Bonus is...
直筆サイン入り チェキ風ブロマイドカードなのら
a handwritten signed Cheki-style bromide card, nora!
みんな ゲットしてほしいのら
I want everyone to get it, nora.
グッズはね 配信終了後 販売開始でーす
Merch sales will start after the stream ends!
そしてそして もう一つ大事なお知らせがあります
And, and! I have one more important announcement.
こちら！
This!
んなっしょいぱっしょん
Nnnna-sshoi Passion!
こちらをね この後歌わせていただきます
I'll be singing this song right after this.
みんなね 大好きな「んなっしょい」っていう言葉使っているのでね
It uses the word "Nnnna-sshoi" that everyone loves,
みんなこの後いっぱい 「んなっしょい」してなー！
so please do lots of "Nnnna-sshoi" afterwards!
この配信がね 終わったらMVも公開されます
The MV will be released once this stream ends.
そして MV公開後もメン限が今回初めてやることになったので
Also, for the first time, I'll be doing a Members-Only stream after the MV release,
こちらも楽しみに！
so look forward to that too!
ではね 歌います
Alright then, I'll sing it.
んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Nnnna-sshoi Passion!
なななな 泣きたい
Na-na-na-na want to cry
別にオチとかねえのら
There's no punchline or anything, nora
んなっしょいぱっしょん
Nnnna-sshoi Passion
むにゃむにゃ 目をこする
Munya munya, rubbing my eyes
囚われた城にパーフェクトな朝
A perfect morning in this captive castle
うないうないお布団
Unai unai futon
飛び出して海へ行こう
Let's jump out and go to the sea
神様だって間違うんだって
Even God makes mistakes, apparently
欲張る話だそうです
Or so the greedy story goes
姫様にね 見惚れちゃうんだって
They get captivated by the Princess, apparently
やれやれだのらね
Good grief, nora
夢を夢見て
Dreaming a dream
恋に恋して生きていたい
I want to live in love with love
だから
So
これでいいのら
this is fine, nora
なななな泣きたい 腹笑いたい
Na-na-na-na want to cry, want to laugh out loud
心だってうりゃって変えるのら
I'll change my heart with a 'Urya' too, nora
だから会いたい その願いに
So I want to see you, for that wish
今 約束の合言葉
Now, the promised password
いくよっ！
Here we go!
んなっしょい！！
Nnnna-sshoi!!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけど
There are slumbering and horror nights too, but
でもね
But you know,
んなっしょい！！
Nnnna-sshoi!!
いつまでもみんな
Everyone will always
おりゅからへいき
be here, so I'm okay
まだ遊び足りねえのら
I haven't played enough yet, nora
んなっしょいぱっしょん
Nnasshoi Passion
来ない来ない 夜の中
In the night that won't come, won't come
ティアラを外して 城を抜けたら
If I take off my tiara and slip out of the castle
深い深い 海に出て
Going out to the deep, deep sea
…バレて野良Knight
...exposed as a stray Knight
姫様はね
The princess is,
わがままなんて
selfish, they say.
おとぎの話よ そうでしょ
That's just a fairy tale, right?
何がなんだって
No matter what,
私なんだって
I am me.
これでいいのら
This is fine, nora.
ななななりたい
I want to become,
私でいたい
I want to be myself.
どこへだって向かってゆけるのら
I can head anywhere I want, nora.
ならば Show Night
Then it's Show Night!
この想いに
For these feelings,
今許される合い言葉
the password that is now allowed.
いくよっ！
Here we go!
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
サンゴ礁
Coral reefs,
白い砂浜も綺麗
the white sandy beach is beautiful too.
そこに
There,
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
輝く私
shining me.
Q. 帰る理由は？
Q. Reason for returning?
A. そこになければねえのら
A. If it's not there, there isn't one, nora!
んなああああい！
Naaaaai!
リピートアフターミー
Repeat after me!
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
せーの
Se-no!
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
もう１回！
One more time!
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
いいねぇ
Nice!
熱い視線が集中
Hot gazes are focusing,
ハラハラする心に夢我夢中
absorbed in a heart that beats fast.
だから
So,
so,
これでいいのら
this is fine, nora.
ななな泣きたい
I want to cry,
から笑いたい
so I want to laugh.
心だって奪ってあげるのら
I'll even steal your heart, nora.
だから会いたい
So I want to meet,
その願いに
for that wish,
今約束の合い言葉
now, the promised password.
いくよー
Here we go!
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
まどろみも
Even slumber,
ほら長い夜も歩ける
look, I can walk through the long night.
でもね
But you know,
んなっしょい！
Nanshoi!
この先もみんな
From now on too, everyone,
Only you から平気
I'm fine because of only you.
まだ遊び足りねえのら
I haven't played enough yet, nora!
生誕ライブ見に来てくれてありがとうなのら！
Thank you for coming to see my birthday live, nora!
今年は体調不良の時期もあったから
Since there was a time I wasn't feeling well this year,
声が出せなかったかもしれない… T_T
I might not have been able to use my voice... T_T
でも最後まで頑張ったのら！！えらいのら！！
But I did my best until the end, nora!! I'm a good girl, nora!!
これからもずーっと姫様に見える忠誠を♥
Please continue to show your loyalty to the Princess forever <3
I love You ちゅぱちゅぱ (・o・(🍬)
I love You chupa-chupa (・o・(🍬)
2025.10.10 るーなのら
2025.10.10 Luna-nora